Do you want to insure your tax on Amazon? It is
very easy to insure your tax on Amazon. If you have
Amazon Pay on your mobile, then definitely
insure your tax on Amazon Pay. So
before that, do not skim through this video and
watch it once so that you do not make any mistake.
And if you have
not yet subscribed to the Sail YouTube channel, then
subscribe quickly and press the bell icon. So
first of all, open Amazon up on your mobile
and simply click on the Amazon Pay written here.
After some pages are loaded, it appears like this. Then
you click on it and go down. Here
in the insurance section,
you simply click on the Tax Insurance written there.
After some pages are loaded, a
new page like this opens. There are
two options here, the first option is Tax and the
second option is Brother. So, you have to
click on the Tax option here and then
write the Tax number below and proceed by
clicking on the View Plane written below. So,
I have written the number here.
Now click on the film below also.  I will
give you some
details to look into, the details of waiting are given here, you do
n't have to do anything here, after doing this you have to come down
and below what is written here confirm and
view quotes click on it and
after clicking a little more a new page opens like this,
here you will see two options, the
first option is comprehensive
plan and the second option is third party
plan, if you want to take comprehensive plan then
what will be your
profit in this, everything is written in detail here,
if other's
car gets damaged in an accident then it will be taxed here,
which it does in third party plan also
and if your car gets damaged then it will be
taxed now, not only this there will be 95% settlement
but the cost of comprehensive plan
is a bit expensive, for this you will have to pay 11000
for 1 year, if you
want to take third party plan then
know now what is the profit in it, you will
not have any profit in this, along with your work,
if someone else's car gets damaged in an accident then
third party plan will also take care of
whatever is necessary in your house and yourself  You will have to pay it, the
profit in this is that the traffic police will
not cut your challan and the
cost of third party plan is very low, see here it will cost
3400 for third party plan for 1
year and GST will have to be paid along with it,
so I select third party plan here
and
click on process below and then see
this kind of interface comes, here it is
written in the first option that if you
want personal accident tax then you will have to pay 399 rupees
more and for this you have to
click on the first option, if you do
not want personal accident tax then there is no need to do it,
click on direct process and after loading it comes like this,
here first of all you have to write your name
which is in the RC, after that you have to write the
name of the person whom you want to keep as nominee here,
then
what is your relation with the nominee, select from here, if there
is a father then select father's name, if there is a mother then select mother's name,
if it is husband or wife then
select this question, you have to
write here below when did the
last policy expire  After writing the expiry date,
select below
which company your previous policy was from.
See, there is a list of many insurance companies listed here,
so
after selecting the previous policy, go down this box
and select whether the
previous policy was comprehensive or third
party, whatever the type was, you have to
select here. If you had done it on loan, then
you have to click on this box,
otherwise leave it blank. Now there is another
box below, you have to click here
because this is the declaration box. You
click on continue below
and after some time loading, a
new page like this opens. You have to scroll down in this page
and below you will
see the payment details.
See, here 5700 GST has been added. Third
party insurance was 3416 and 399 rupees
personal accident tax and with that 6700
GST, total is 4502. So
you will have to pay the money for third party insurance.
Now simply click on the procedure below
and  After doing some more digging, the
payment page opens. You
can make UPSC payment here. If you want, you
can also make payment with an ATM card. There is
also a net banking option below,
so I will
demonstrate how to make a payment using a bank account linked with Amazon Pay. That is why
I have clicked on the Amazon Pay app.
Now click on the PAN and K below.
After some loading, the app's page opens. So
learn here. Okay, after writing 4 digital EPF P,
click on the right button. After
some loading, the payment is
completed.
After doing some more digging, the insurance papers appear on the screen. Save that
PF file
on your mobile and later print it and
keep it with your tax. I hope you have
understood how to do it with Amazon.
If you like the video, do
n't forget to like and share it. For such useful
videos, subscribe to our YouTube channel and
press the bell icon.
Thank you.